A Finding Aid to the Exhibition Records of the Contemporary Study Wing of the Finch College Museum of Art, 1943-1975, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
- Elayne Varian Personal Papers, 1965-1970; Series 3; Archival Resource Key; 1.3 Linear feet Boxes 5-6
  A single file of teaching materials consists of a syllabus and course schedule.
  The bulk of writings in the series consist of recorded interviews, with corresponding transcripts, of art dealers and artists, which were conducted for a 1970 article Varian wrote for Art in America called "New Dealing," on the subject of artist-dealer relationships. Interviews, listed individually in the folder list, are on 11 sound tape reels and are typically around 40 minutes in duration. Photographs related to that project are also found depicting Virginia Dwan, Martha Jackson, and Leo Castelli with Andy Warhol. Other writing projects include published interviews with artists Brian O'Doherty and Babette Newburger, a manual on museum security, and an article on patented art. The original interview with Newburger is found on one sound tape reel with an edited transcript.
  - Curation outside of Finch College, Archival Resource Key (Box 5)
    - New York State Fair, "Art Today" (1967), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Everson Museum Film Series, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Everson Museum Film Series, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Guild Hall, "21 Over 60" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Guild Hall, "21 Over 60" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Guild Hall, "21 Over 60" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Teaching, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Writings, Archival Resource Key
    - Book Review of Arte Povera, circa 1965-circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Interview with Brian O'Doherty for Art International, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Lecture for Wagner College, circa 1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Museum Security, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Museum Security, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - "New Dealing" for Art in America (1970 Jan), Archival Resource Key
      - Correspondence, 1969-1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 13)
      - Interview with Leo Castelli, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 14)
      - Edited Transcript of Castelli Interview for the Archives of American Art, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 5, Folder 15)
      - Interview with Virginia Dwan, 1969 April; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 16)
      - Interview with John Gibson, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 17)
      - Interview with Richard Feigen, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 18)
      - Interview with Arnold Glimcher and Fred Mueller of Pace Gallery, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 19)
      - Interview with Adolph Gottlieb, 1969 May 20; Archival Resource Key; Transcript (Box 5, Folder 20)
        Recording of Gottlieb interview is found on sound tape reel with Charles Ross interview
      - Interview with Martha Jackson, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 21)
      - Interview with Sidney Janis, 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 22)
      - Interview with Roy Lichtenstein, 1969 May 20; Archival Resource Key; Transcript (Box 5, Folder 23)
        Recording of Lichtenstein interview is found on sound tape reel with Charles Ross interview
      - Interview with Betty Parsons, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 24)
      - Interview with Charles Ross, 1969 May 20; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 25)
        Sound tape reel also contains Gottlieb and Lichtenstein interviews, whose transcripts are filed under their names.
      - Interview with Seth Siegelaub, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - "New Dealing" for Art in America (1970 Jan), Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
      - Interview with Howard Wise, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 6, Folder 1)
      - Interview Notes, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 2)
      - Handwritten Drafts, circa 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 3)
      - Typescript Drafts, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 4)
      - Photographs and Captions, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 5)
        Contains a negative of a photograph of Virginia Dwan taken by Nancy Smithson, photographs of Martha Jackson with Claire Falkenstein, Paul Jenkins, and Antoni Tapies, and slides of Andy Warhol with Leo Castelli.
      - Research, 1968-1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Patented Art, 1965, 1969; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 7)
      Contains notes from an interview with Sue Fuller
    - "Plastics for Everyday Living: Babette Newberger" for Art in America (1969 August), Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound tape reel Includes transcript (Box 6, Folder 8)
      A published interview with Newberger conducted by Elaine Varian
- Exhibition Files, 1943-1975; Series 4; Archival Resource Key; 14.9 Linear feet Boxes 6-22, OV 24-25, FC 26
  Series is arranged alphabetically by exhibition title, with materials for each exhibition arranged by type. Selected exhibition catalogs are also arranged alphabetically at the beginning of the series. The records of each exhibition are arranged slightly differently, and what arrangement was found is retained, with folder headings sometimes changed for clarity. Additional exhibition files for shows curated by Elayne Varian outside of Finch College are found in series 3, Elayne Varian personal papers.
  The bulk of this series has been digitized, except for duplicates and blank versos of photographs. The "selected exhibition catalogs" in folders 9-14 were not digitized because they are duplicates of catalogs that can be found in the folders arranged alphabetically by exhibition title. In some cases, catalogs for exhibitions that were not at Finch College and other publications have only had their covers, title pages, and relevant pages digitized.
  All of the sound and video recordings found in this series have been digitized and are available for research use. The motion picture film documenting Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Structure (1966) has also been digitized.
  Series contains records documenting the creation and public exhibition of shows at the Contemporary Wing galleries from its inception in 1964 to its close in 1975, as well as records for several exhibitions that were in development but not yet realized when the college closed. Documentation includes artist files, checklists, correspondence, writings, exhibition catalogs, photographs, interviews, films and videos documenting exhibitions or created for exhibition, artist statements, loan documentation, insurance documentation, and publicity in the form of press releases, exhibition announcements, clippings, and posters. A run of exhibition catalogs filed at the beginning of the series represent about half of the exhibitions held in the Contemporary Wing. Catalogs are also found filed under each exhibition's title for most of the exhibitions in the series, often annotated with insurance values or in various drafts.
  Unlike the artist files in series 2, artist files specific to exhibitions tend to contain richer documentation, including writings and original correspondence with the artist, artist statements, photographs, or information about particular artworks.
  Interviews are found on 9 sound cassettes and 14 sound tape reels scattered in the exhibition files, all conducted by Elayne Varian and relating to the exhibition at hand. They include Alan Sonfist ("Alan Sonfist: Time Landscape"), Mel Bochner ("Art in Process IV), Hans Richter ("Hans Richter Retrospective"), Ruth Richards on Hugo Weber ("Hugo Weber Retrospective), James Brooks and Janet Katz ("James Brooks Retrospective," transcript only), Physicists Lloyd G. Cross, Allyn Z. Lite, and Gerald Thomas Bern Pethick ("N-Dimensional Space), Margaret Benyon ("N-Dimensional Space"), Irwin Hollander (transcript only, "Prints from Hollander's Workshop"), David Anderson ("The Private Collection of Martha Jackson"), Doris Chase ("Projected Art: Artists at Work"), and Will Insley, Michael Kirby, Les Levine, Ursula Meyer, Brian O'Doherty, Charles Ross, and Tony Smith ("Schemata 7"); Douglas Davis, Jane Davis, and Russ Connor ("Talk-Out!"); Les Levine ("The Troubles"); Michael Mazur and Paul Gedeohn ("Two Aspects of An Illusion"). An additional sound recording describing the installation and content of the exhibition "Towers" is found on one sound tape reel.
  In addition to the recorded interviews, a number of moving image recordings are found. The video in Artists' Videotape Performances (1971) is a complex mix of recordings, ranging from simple, single-channel video works that were played in the gallery, to components of multi-channel installations, artifacts of interactive sound and video installations, and recordings of performances put on in the gallery. Other motion pictures found in the series include videos of artists Sam Weiner, Lynda Benglis, and Michael Singer working in Projected Art: Artists at Work (1971), and film of the installed exhibition Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Structure (1966). In total, motion pictures in this series are on 19 videoreels (1/2 inch), 2 film reels (16 mm, with VHS and Digital Betacam videocassette access copies).
  Other artworks or components of artworks found include original writings by Dan Graham in Art in Series (1967-1968) and mail art by Richard Merkin and Ray Johnson in Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Collage (1967). Artists books found in the series include Statements by Lawrence Weiner and Identikit by Jim Brodey, found in Lynda Benglis' artist file; both of these publications are with records for Art in Process IV (1969-1970). Schematic drawings, floor plans, and installation instructions are found for Robert Morris for Art in Process V (1972) Douglas Davis and several other artists for Artists' Videotape Performances (1971), Michael Kirby for Schemata 7 (1967), Stan Vanderbeek for Projected Art (1966-1967), and various works for N-Dimensional Space (1970).
  - Selected Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Selected Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Selected Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Selected Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Selected Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Selected Exhibition Catalogs, 1964-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - "Agnes Denes" (not realized), circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - "Alan Sonfist: Time Landscape" (1975, Not realized at Finch College), Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - Artist File, 1971-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Correpondence, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Interview with Sonfist, circa 1974; Archival Resource Key; 1 Sound cassette (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Project File, 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - "American Art Deco Architecture" (1974-1975), Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - Catalog Drafts and Final Catalog, circa 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - New York State Council on the Arts Grant, 1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Photographs, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Photographs, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Photographs, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Photographs, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Photographs, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Photographs, circa 1974-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 27)
      Oversized photographs housed in box 22, folder 3.
  - "Arshile Gorky Drawings" (not realized), 1967, 1973-1975; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - "Art Deco" (1970), Archival Resource Key (Box 6)
    - Bills and Receipts, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Catalog Drafts and Final Catalog, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 30)
      Oversized galleys housed in box 22, folder 3
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 31)
      See also loan documentation for additional correspondence.
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence, 1970-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Insurance, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Lists, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 6, Folder 35)
      Oversized lists in box 22, folder 3
    - Loans, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
      - Loan Forms, B, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 1)
      - Loan Forms, B-C, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 2)
      - Loan Forms, E-H, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 3)
      - Loan Forms, I-K, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 4)
      - Loan Forms, K-L, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 5)
      - Loan Forms, M-N, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 6)
      - Loan Forms, N-O, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Loan Forms, P-S, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 8)
      - Loan Forms, T-W, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 9)
      - Outstanding Loan Forms, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 10)
      - Small Lenders, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 11)
      - Lender Lists, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 12)
      - Anonymous, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 13)
      - Peter Brant, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 14)
      - Edward Lee Cave, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 15)
      - Cooper-Hewitt Museum of Design, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 16)
      - Galerie Sonnabend, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Solomon R. Guggenheim Museum, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Stanley Insler, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Rockwell Kent / Larcada Gallery, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 20)
      - Lillian Nassau, Ltd., 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 21)
      - Richard Merkin, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 22)
      - Metropolitan Museum, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 23)
      - Metropolitan Museum, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 24)
      - Museum of Modern Art, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 25)
      - John Nicolas Streep, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 26)
      - Barbara Streisand / Sybarites, Inc., 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 27)
      - Andy Warhol, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 28)
      - Louis Winter, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Photographs, circa 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Press Release and Clippings, 1970-1972; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 31)
      Oversized clippings housed in OV 23, folder 8.
    - Research, 1967-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Research, 1967-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Research, 1967-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Slide Script by American Craft Council, 1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Traveling Exhibition, Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
      - Loan Agreements, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 36)
      - Loan Agreements, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 37)
      - Loan Agreements, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 38)
      - Cranbrook Academy, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 39)
      - Cranbrook Academy, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 40)
      - Cranbrook Academy, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 41)
      - Cranbrook Academy, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 42)
      - Cranbrook Academy, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 43)
      - Cranbrook Academy, 1970; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - Minneapolis Institute of Arts, 1970-1971; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 45)
        Oversized clippings housed in OV 23, folder 9.
  - "Art from Belgium" (1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 7)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Lists, circa 1964; Archival Resource Key (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - "Art from Belgium" (1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - Printed Material and Photographs and Catalog, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Receipts, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - "Art from Finland" (1973), Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - Catalog and Clippings, 1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 3)
      Oversized clipping housed in box 22, folder 3
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence, 1972-1974; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Insurance and Loan Forms, 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Photographs, circa 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Photographs, circa 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Photographs, circa 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Photographs, circa 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Photographs, circa 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Photographs, circa 1972-1973; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - "Art from the Chase Manhattan Bank Collection" (1971), Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - "Art in Jewelry" (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
      - Gordon Andrews, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 17)
      - Friedrich Becker, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 18)
      - Friedrich Becker, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 19)
      - Georges Braque, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 20)
        Oversized clippings housed in OV 23, folder 10.
      - Maurice Brault, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 21)
      - Roberto Burle-Marx, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Salvador Dali, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 23)
      - Bert Gore, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 24)
      - Gubelin (Martha Widmer), 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 25)
      - Gubelin (Martha Widmer), 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 26)
      - Paula Haivaoja, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 27)
      - Anne Kursmo, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 28)
      - Octave Landuyt, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 29)
      - Ole Lynggard, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 30)
      - Bruno Martinazzi, 1965-1967; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 31)
      - Marianne Ostier, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 32)
      - Marianne Ostier, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 33)
      - Gillian Packard, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 34)
      - Sigurd Persson, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 35)
      - Antonio Pineda, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 36)
      - Sepp Schmoelzer, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 37)
      - Reiko Yamada, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Biographies, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Catalog and Press Release, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Catalog Drafts, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Clippings, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 42)
      Oversized clippings housed in OV 23, folder 11.
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Customs, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Customs, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Lists, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Photographs, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Printers, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Painting" (1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 8)
    - Artist's Statements, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 52)
      Contains handwritten artist statements by Jim Dine, Grace Hartigan, George Ortman, Jack Sonenberg, Reva Urban, and Jack Youngerman.
    - Biographies, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Catalog and Clippings, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Correspondence, 1964-1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Painting" (1965), Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Insurance Evaluations, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Lists, circa 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Loan Agreement Forms, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Photographs and Source Material, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Press Release and Announcement, 1965; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - "Art in Process: The Visual Development of a Structure" (1966), Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
    - Artist Files, Archival Resource Key (Box 9)
      - Possibilities, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 6)
      - Stephen Antonakos, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 7)
      - Richard Artschwager, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Richard Baringer, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Mary Bauermeister, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - Chryssa, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - Dan Flavin, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - Paul Frazier, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - Charles Hinman, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - Will Insley, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - Donald Judd, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - Lyman Kipp, 1962-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - Sol Le Witt, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - Sven Lukin, circa 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - Victor Millonzi, 1966-1968; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - Robert Morris, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - Otto Piene, 1965-1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - Robert Smithson, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - Robert Watts, 1966; Archival Resource Key (Box 9, Folder 24)